question_data = [
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "The name of the main character of the video game &quot;The Legend of Zelda&quot;, is Zelda.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Comics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
         "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The term &quot;Spam&quot; came before the food product &quot;Spam&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio&#039;s character hunts down the killer of his son.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Liechtenstein does not have an airport.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot; and &quot;The Legend of Korra&quot;, Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
         "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
